<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="faq">
        <item name="getAccount_title">&lt;b>I do not have an account. How do I get one?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="getAccount_text">Due to the reason that you can trigger amateur radio transmissions with your account, please apply for an account by emailing to rwth-afu [at] online.de and provide some prove that you are a licensed amateur radio operator. Also give your Pager ID (RIC) as you can see here: </item>
        <item name="accountEmail_title">&lt;b>I emailed 10 minutes ago. No answer yet. How long does it take to get an account?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="accountEmail_text">We review the applications in our free time. So please be patient for some days.</item>
        <item name="whatCallSign_title">&lt;b>What is a callsign?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="whatCallSign_text">A callsign is logical connection between a name (the callsign) and one or multiple RIC numbers.</item>
        <item name="whatTransmitter_title">&lt;b>What is a transmitter?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="whatTransmitter_text">A transmitter is a device that puts the POCSAG signal on the air. There are many hardware configurations, like C9000, RasPager. Have a look at https://www.afu.rwth-aachen.de/projekte/funkruf-pager-pocsag.</item>
        <item name="whatRIC_title">&lt;b>What is a RIC?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="whatRIC_text">A RIC is the identification number in the POCSAG world. They can have special meaning like the clock-RIC to set the date and time on your pager. Mostly they identify personally your pager. The assignment between a personal RIC and you is the "Callsign".</item>
        <item name="addCallSign_title">&lt;b>I cannot add a callsign or a transmitter.&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="addCallSign_text">Due to abuse reasons, only admins can add callsigns or transmitters. Please contact rwth-afu [at] online.de. Once your callsign or transmitter is assigned to you, you can edit it by yourself.</item>
        <item name="addTransmitter_title">&lt;b>I want to add a transmitter to the network.&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="addTransmitter_text">"Very nice. We like the network growing. Please send an email to rwth-afu [at] online.de and give the following information:

    Callsign of the transmitter
    Location Latitude and Longitude (Please in decimal form, e.g. 50.12345)
    Type of transmitter: Widerange (> 1 watt) oder Personal (≤1 watt, e.g. RasPager)
    Transmitter output power in watt
    Antenna type (omni or directional)
    Height of the antenna above ground (!), not above sea level
    Gain of the antenna minus cable losses in dBi
    Desired time slots (Please have a look here http://www.hampager.de/#/transmitters/map and find out, which timeslots in your neighborhood are already used.) If you are unsure, just let us know and we will find a suitable solution."</item>
        <item name="addNode_title">&lt;b>I want to add a node to the network.&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="addNode_text">Please send an email to rwth-afu [at] online.de and give the following information:

    Amateur radio callsign.
    Location Latitude and Longitude (Please in decimal form, e.g. 50.12345)
    Some reason, why it makes sense to add your node.

Keep in mind that you need a stable HAMNET connection (44.0.0.0/8) to join the cluster network.</item>
        <item name="noRubrics_title">&lt;b>I do not receive the rubrics on my skyper.&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="noRubrics_text">Please activate your skyper on http://www.hampager.de/#/rubrics using the "Activate Rubrics" function. You have to provide your pager ID (RIC).</item>
        <item name="addRubric_title">&lt;b>I want to add a rubric to the network.&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="addRubric_text">Please send an email to rwth-afu [at] online.de and give the following information:

    The desired name
    The content you want to provide
    The transmitter group on which you want to send out your data</item>
        <item name="sendingAuto_title">&lt;b>I want to send automated messages from third party sources.&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="sendingAuto_text">You can use the REST API to do so. Description here: https://github.com/DecentralizedAmateurPagingNetwork/Core/wiki/Beschreibung-der-REST-API. Please be aware that the traffic capability is limited on the air interface. So make fair use and use a transmitter group that fits to your needs. Nobody wants in transmitter group "all" the information that someone has phoned you or your washing machine is done.</item>
        <item name="whatTimeSlot_title">&lt;b>What is a timeslot?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="whatTimeSlot_text">As all transmitters work on the same frequency (TDMA), only one transmitter can be active at a time to avoid interference. This is why there are 16 timeslots (0 to F) assigned to each transmitter. If you operate a transmitter it is mandatory to have your clock synced by NTP. Otherwise you will destroy the network.</item>
        <item name="whichTimeSlot_title">&lt;b>How do I know which timeslots to use on a transmitter?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="whichTimeSlot_text">Please have a look here http://www.hampager.de/#/transmitters/map and find out, which timeslots in your neighborhood are already used.)</item>
        <item name="whereHardware_title">&lt;b>I want to get a plug-and-play hardware for a new transmitter site. Where can I get it from?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="whereHardware_text">There is an easy solution with GM1200 and a RasPi. If you like to get a 19 Inch Rack, please send an email to dbwr [at] darc.de. An example can be found here https://www.afu.rwth-aachen.de/projekte/funkruf-pager-pocsag/funkrufsender-19-zoll-mit-gm1200.</item>
        <item name="whereSkyper_title">&lt;b>Where can I get a Skyper?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="whereSkyper_text">Please help yourself. There is a possibility to buy at www.funkhandel.com.</item>
        <item name="whySkyper_title">&lt;b>Why is the time displayed on my Skyper wrong?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="whySkyper_text">It is not wrong, it\'s UTC. We know, there are pros and cons of using UTC, but this is the most common understanding.</item>
        <item name="someRubrics_title">&lt;b>Some rubics are not transmitted on my transmitter.&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="someRubrics_text">Please check, if your transmitter is in a member of all desired transmitter groups that are assigned to a rubric. Especially for the DX-Cluster messages, there were complains about heavy load on some transmitters. So we added another transmitter group of the DX-Cluster messages. If you want to transmit those messages, have your transmitter added to the group.</item>
        <item name="longTransmitBug_title">&lt;b>Sometimes my transmitter transmits longer than the assigned timeslots.&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="longTransmitBug_text">We are aware of this bug. It is tracked in this issue: https://github.com/rwth-afu/UniPager/issues/66 and will be hopefully solved soon.</item>
        <item name="SMTPSend_title">&lt;b>Is there an SMTP-Interface to DAPNET, so I can send calls with my email program?&lt;/b></item>
        <item name="SMTPSend_text">Not yet. Feel free to contribute. Use the open documented REST-API and write a simple SMTP server generating REST calls to the API.&lt;/b></item>
    </string-array>
</resources>